GWACHUKWU IKENNA ELEBEKE

10B Latunde Close, Ago Palace Way, Okota, Lagos. +2347030821996 / +2348153045001

gwachukwuelebeke@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/gwachukwu LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/gwachukwu Portfolio: https://gwachukwu.github.io/Portfolio

PROFILE

Full -stack web developer with experience working with HTML, CSS3/SASS, JavaScript, React, NodeJS, ExpressJS, NoSQL (MongoDB) and SQL (Postgres), I build amazing and user-friendly web applications. I am also skilled in Computer Networking (Routing and Switching), Microsoft Azure, Sales and Customer Service. I enjoy working on new products, and occasionally taking on new challenges that push me to grow.

SKILLS

Web Development

HTML, CSS3, SASS, VANILLA JAVASCRIPT, REACT, VUE, JSX REDUX, PHP

NODEJS, EXPRESS, SQL (Postgres, MySQL), NoSQL (MongoDB).

Computer Networking

Network engineering, Routing protocols (EIGRP, OSPF, BGP etc.),

Operational support, Multicasting knowledge (IPv4 and IPv6), Virtual networking, TCP/IP, NAT, ACL etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Aug 2020 - present

Cerebre Digital Limited, Opebi, Ikeja, Lagos State.

- Full stack development with HTML5, CSS3/SASS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP
- Use MySQL and PostgreSQL for database development
- Build software that meet clients' specifications

Software Engineer Nov 2019 - Aug 2020

Stutern Graduate Accelerator, Gbagada, Lagos State.

- Full stack development with HTML5, CSS3/SASS,
- Bootstrap4, React, NodeJS, Express.
- Used PostgreSQL/MongoDB for databases development.
- Developed and designed Restful API.
- Collaborating on GitHub, Trello and Slack.

Information and Communications Technology Instructor 2018 KingChuks College Okota, Lagos State

- Managed institution's ICT networks and infrastructures
- Taught ICT as a subject.

National Youth Service Corps: Educational Instructor 2016-2017

Gaskiya Model School, Katsina, Katsina State.

- Developed good mentoring and instructional skills
- Taught Physics and Chemistry

TRAININGS

SheHacks Africa Cohort 13 09/2019 (Access bank, Waaw and ACT foundations scholarship)

Web Development – HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP. MvSQL.

Leadership and Entrepreneurship training

Andela Learning Community with Google 05/2020

Google Africa Developer Scholarship (Mobile Web Specialist)

Andela Learning Community with Microsoft 06/2020

Microsoft Azure Training Program

PROJECTS

Magnitude: React, Node.js, Express, Postgres.

Event centers application.

https://magnitude-event-centers.netlify.app

Sound Vault: React, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB.

Audio cloud service application. https://sound-vault.netlify.app

Gwachukwu's bank: React, NodeJS,

Express, MongoDB.

A finance tracking app.

https://gwachukwus-bank.netlify.app

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Certified Network Associate (Routing and Switching) 2019

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals 2020

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

BSc. Industrial Chemistry
University of Benin, Benin city, Edo State,
Nigeria 2015